Guide to the Stanford University, Department of Biology, Honors Theses
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Department of Biology, honors theses
1978-2013
SC4-3705
Stanford University. Department of Biology.
70 Linear feet
Honors theses written by undergraduates in the Stanford University Department of Biology.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
This collection was transferred to the Stanford University Archives by the Department of Biology. Additional theses were transferred from the Hume Writing Center in 2011.
Information about Access
The collection is open for research; materials must be requested at least 48 hours in advance of intended use. No photocopies may be made.
Scope and Contents note
This collection consists of honors theses written by undergraduates in the Stanford University Department of Biology.
Access Terms
Biology.; Student papers.
Collection Contents
- Theses, Acessions ARCH-1991-097
  - Albright, Shane R., The Role of Glycosylation in the Response of Murine Melanoma Cells to Transforming Growth Factor B., June 1991 (Box 1)
  - Baker, Felix, Mapping the repair of psoralen photoadducts with the DHFR domaine of CHO cells., June 1991 (Box 1)
  - Banatoski, Jill M., Heparan sulfate proteoglycan: a link between diabetes mellitus and atherosclerosis?., May 1991 (Box 1)
  - Bisla, Kammi, A new in vitro whole mount corneal preparation to study the effects of local anesthetic on corneal epithelial wound healing., June 1991 (Box 1)
  - Chamberlain, John R., Dose response to ultraviolet irradiation in the spec gene family of s. purpuratus sperm., June 1991 (Box 1)
  - Chang, Alan T., 8-OH-DPAT reversal of propranolol effects on male rat sexual behavior., June 1991 (Box 1)
  - Chuang, John, Characterization of ultrabithorax activated transcripts in drosophila melanogaster., June 1991 (Box 1)
  - Cohen, Amanda, A model of phytoplankton population dynamics in the euphotic zone of Monterey Bay., June 1991 (Box 1)
  - Duda, Greg, Control of the level of immune response in schistosomiasis., June 1991 (Box 1)
  - Flannery, Brendan, Implications for a plasma membrane sperm receptor on Ascidia ceratodes eggs., March 1991 (Box 1)
  - Fong, Katherine Janice, Genetic analysis of thermoresistance at the cellular level., June 1991 (Box 1)
  - Ford, Michael J., Mitochondrial DNA evolution in lepidoptera: evolutionary rates and colias systematics., June 1991 (Box 1)
  - Frutkin, Andrew Dylan, Anti-granulocyte-macrophage colony-stimulating factor monoclonal antibody protects BALB/c mice against lethal effects of salmonella abortus equi lipopolysaccharide., June 1991 (Box 1)
  - Grancell, Adam S., B-Endorphin: a conformational study using computer simulation., June 1991 (Box 1)
  - Ha, Taryn Phuong-Thao, Glucocorticoid effects on hippocampal astrocytes: decreased affinity of glutamate uptake in hypoglycemic conditions., June 1991 (Box 1)
  - Haddad, Nick, Effects of surrounding habitats on bird distributions in islands of oak woodland., June 1991 (Box 1)
  - Hein, Anthony Nicholas, Experimental autoimmune and passive immune models of epidermal growth factor (EGF) deficiency: effects on late gestation and neonatal rats., June 1991 (Box 2)
  - Judson, Olivia, Does the scrub jay, Aphelocoma coerulescens, use ultraviolet vision for the detection and selection of acorns?., June 1991 (Box 2)
  - Karpa, Doug, Retrogressive primary succession and alien species invasion in a Hawaiian montane grassland., June 1991 (Box 2)
  - Kim, David H., A study of DNA markers in a Cambodian population., June 1991 (Box 2)
  - Kim, Joanne Y., Molecular structural basis of ligand selectivity for 5-HT2 versus 5-HT1c corical receptors., June 1991 (Box 2)
  - Lai, Stephen Y., Insulin-like growth factor 1 receptor: the biological consequences associated with altered glycosylation., June 1991 (Box 2)
  - Lee, Mark, The effects of psychoactive drugs on the circadian rhythm in Neurospora crassa., June 1991 (Box 2)
  - Lee, Michael Young-June, Evaluation of peripheral nerve neurite outgrowth promoting activity by development of an in vitro bioassay using intact rat dorsal root ganglia., May 1991 (Box 2)
  - Leung, Gordon K., the effects of 1-alpha, 25-(OH)2 vitamin D3 on human prostatic epithelial cells., June 1991 (Box 2)
  - Lindes, Deborah S., Functional characterization of a carboxy-terminal truncation mutant of a 70-kilodalton heat shock cognate protein., June 1991 (Box 2)
  - Lum, Daryl Wynn, Glycosylation structure, and its effects on alpha4beta1, a receptor, for the heparin binding domain of fibronectin., June 1991 (Box 2)
  - Mozaffarian, Dariush, ACTH secretion in the neonatal rat: the effects of maternal deprivation., June 1991 (Box 2)
  - Oliker, Rachel, Reduction of slowly-triggered glutamate neurotoxicity by nordihydroguaiaretic acid., June 1991 (Box 2)
  - Peng, Stanford L., Atttachment site of phage 21., June 1991 (Box 2)
  - Peters, Maurice Robert, Cloning and partial characterization of the leucine operon of Aquaspirillum magnetotacticum., June 1991 (Box 2)
  - Quan, Jeanette, Regulation of Sm autoantigen isoform expression during cell cycle., June 1991 (Box 2)
  - Roberts, Jennifer S., Cell migration in cultured cerebral cortical slices., June 1991 (Box 2)
  - Shen, Yu-Min P., XPE binding factor: a protein involved in DNA excision repair and tumor metastasis., June 1991 (Box 3)
  - Shimizu, Mari, An analysis of the formation of excitatory abnd inhibitory synapses in the turtle cortex during development., June 1991 (Box 3)
  - Stoker, David A., The effects of systemic propranolol on sexual behavior in male rats., June 1991 (Box 3)
  - Waikar, Manoj, Different receptors for 5-hydroxytryptamine and tryptamine in rat isolated fundic strip., June 1991 (Box 3)
  - Winkes, Ben, A single cell assay for x-inactivation in preimiplantation mouse embryos., June 1991 (Box 3)
  - Woods, Arthur, the effects of mating frequency in males of Heliconius charitonius., June 1991 (Box 3)
  - Yew, Ken, Regulation of macrophage lipoprotein lipase by protein kinase C., June 1991 (Box 3)
  - Yun, Paul, Intracerebroventricular administration of D,L-propranolol: effects on male rat sexual behavior., June 1991 (Box 3)
- Theses, Accession ARCH-1992-096
  - Arora, Shobhit, The Effects of Exercise and Sleep Deprivation on the Re-Entrainment of Circadian Rhythms in the Rat., March, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Beaulieu, Stacy E., Quantitative Measurement of the Concentration Fields Above a Bed of Model Bivalves., June, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Brown, Rhett E., Analysis of mutants affecting the expression of a developmentally regulated gene in Neurospora crassa., June 1992 (Box 1)
  - Castro,Marisol Robles, Reconstruction of SCID Mice with Human PBL to Develop a Functional in Vivo System for Studying Human CD4+ T Cell Subsets During Immunizaton.., June, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Chang, Felicia, A Study of the Minimal Bacterial Attachment Site of Phage 21., June 1992 (Box 1)
  - Chang, Lihchun Micheal, Characterization of PBP-5, a Putative Polyadenylate Binding Protein in Drosophila Melanogaster.., June 4, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Chen, Clark Chin-Chung, Murine Intestinal Mucins Inhibit Rotavirus Infection.., May 1992 (Box 1)
  - Chen, James S., Development of a Novel Monoclonal Antibody to Human Blood Dendritic Cells.., June 1992 (Box 1)
  - Cheng, Elbert, Regulation of Hepatic LDL Receptor Gene Expression by Serum Growth Factors.., june 1992 (Box 1)
  - Choi, Paul D., Identidication of Immune Cells Involved in the Inflammatory Response Generated by Combined Corynebacterium parvum and Recombinant Interleukin-2.., June 1992 (Box 1)
  - Chu, Eugene S., Hypothermia Induces a Breakdown of Mammalian Central Nervous System Electrical Activity.., June 1992 (Box 1)
  - Clark, Kathryn M., The Effects of Hybrid Robertsonian Fusion on Fertility in Mus musculus domesticus., May 1992 (Box 1)
  - Copass, Michael, Plasmid-Mediated Entry of Yersinia pseudotuberculosis into Eukaryotic Cells.., June 1992 (Box 1)
  - Cravatt, Benjamin, Peptide-Peptide Interactions within the T Cell Receptor Complex.., June 1992 (Box 1)
  - DiGregorio, David, Increasing GFAF mRNA with Increasing Severity of EAE Episodes.., June 1992 (Box 1)
  - Fleming, Anne, The Subcellar Localization of Low Molecular Weight GTP-binding Protein o-rab3 in AtT-20 Cells.., June 1992 (Box 1)
  - Gaus, Stephanie E., Circadian Rhythms and Sleep Architecture in Rats with Hereditary Diabetes Insipidus (Brattleboro Strain).., June 1992 (Box 1)
  - Hamerman, Jessica A., Non-Coordinate Regulation of Murine Class II Molecules and Ia-Associated Invariant Chain by Cyclic Amp and Prostaglandin E2.., June 1992 (Box 1)
  - Haspel, Richard, Anti-CD8 Antibody Treatment Rduces the Effects if T Cell Receptor Peptide Vaccination.., June 1992 (Box 1)
  - Hsu, Judith Wyne-chi, Development of a Novel Assay for the Quantitation of Alpha-2 Adrenergic Receptors in the Locus Coeruleus of the Rat.., June 4, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Irwin, Darren, The Evolution of Phosphoglucose Isomerase within Pierine Butterflies.., June 1992 (Box 2)
  - Jan, Amy Y., Molecular Modeling of Apolipoprotein(a) Kringle-Type 9 and Possible Interactions With Apo-B 100.., May 1992 (Box 2)
  - Kacker, Sonia, CNS Location of the Effects of Beta-Adrenergic Receptor Blockers Pindolol and Ateneolo on Rat Mating Behavior.., June 1992 (Box 2)
  - Kayser, Andrew S., The Effects of Altered Sequence on the Anterior localization of bicoid mRNA in Drosophilia.., June 1992 (Box 2)
  - Kim, Ivana, Enzymatic Basis for Altered Glycosylation in a Wheat Germ Agglutinin Resistant Variant of D16 Mouse Melanoma.., December 1991 (Box 2)
  - Kueny, Tucker, The Effects of Chronically Administered Propanolol on Sexual Behavior in Male Rats.., June 1992 (Box 2)
  - Lee, Eric W., Catalytic Subunits of Aplysia cAMP-Dependent Protein Kinase with Two Different N-Termini., October 30, 1991 (Box 2)
  - Lenox, Marlo, Resolution Studies of a Visible Light Imagining System Using Time-Constrained Tim-of-Flight Spectrophotometry., June, 1992 (Box 2)
  - Levine, Edward Harris, T Cell Suppression Alters the Panel of Cytokines Expressed by Stimulated CD4+ Cells., June, 1992 (Box 2)
  - Levitt, Diana Beth, Exclusion Mapping of the Rett Syndrome Gene Locus on the X Chromosome., June, 1992 (Box 2)
  - Liu, Taylor I., GFAP Immunoreactivity in Octopus rubescens Nervous System., June, 1992 (Box 2)
  - Lo, Jonathan I., Mapping of an HTLV-I p19 Epitope with a Human Monoclonal Antibody., May, 1990 (Box 2)
  - Lozier, Alan Paul, The Development of Thalamocorticol Projetions: Data from the Rat's Somatosensory System and the Two-Process Model of Cortical Innervation., May, 1992 (Box 2)
  - Mahmood, Naveen Sultana, Characterization of the Molecular Starvation Response in Marine Vibrios., May 28, 1992 (Box 2)
  - Nelson, Larry I., Developmental Expression of Slow Myosin 3.., June 1992 (Box 2)
  - Nunez, Stefanie, Oligosaccharide Microheterogeneity in Murine Ia Antigens:Determination of the Ebeta Polypeptide Region Responsible for Haplotype-Specific Glycosylation in Ealpha.., June 1992 (Box 2)
  - O'Keefe, F.Robin, Analysis of Nectar Stading Crop in Helenium hoopsii: Spatially Independent Standing Crop Variation Over Time.., June 1992 (Box 2)
  - Pearson, Margaret, The Search for Mutations in the Fibrillin Gene in Patients with Marfan Syndrome.., June 1992 (Box 2)
  - Pinto, Jayant Marian, Steroid Binding Protein Genes in Yeast: Evidence for an Estrogen Binding Protein Gene in Candida tropicalis.., June 5, 1992 (Box 2)
  - Rahman, Maie A. and George M. Hahn, Down-Regulation of HSP70kDa Does Not Induce Increased Sensitivity to Adriamycin in Murine Radiation-Induced Fibrosarcoma Cells.., May 1992 (Box 3)
  - Rangarajan, Radha, Role of Chloride Chanels in the Organization of the Circadian Rhythm of Neuronal Activity in the Suprachiasmatic Nuclei.., June 3, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Rao, Rekha C., Linkage of Autism to Restriction Fragment Length Polymorphism Markers on Chromosome 7.., June 1992 (Box 3)
  - Raskin, Alexander, Effects of Intracerebroventricular Injections of Propranolol and Metroprolol on Male Rat Sexual Behavior.., June 1992 (Box 3)
  - Rawa, Agnieszka, Generation and Isolation of Dominant Myosin Mutants in Dictyostelium.., June 1992 (Box 3)
  - Redish, Deborah M., The Effect of Glucocorticoids on Metabolism in Normal and Transformed Fibroblasts.., June 1992 (Box 3)
  - Reisner, Andrew, A novel strategy to obtain accurate anthropometric data in use with cycling experiments.., June 7, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Seielstad, Mark T., A Molecular Systematic Study of the Colias alexandra Species Complex: Toward an Understanding of the Interactions Between Phyletic and Adaptive Diversity., June, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Shingal, Rajesh, Ceramide Metabolism in the Synapse.., June, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Suen, Patrick W.; Niels C. Krejci; Rosalind A Grymes; Joseph McGuire; and Eugene A. Bauer, Type I Collagenase Expression Correlates with Fibroblast Migration., June, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Sun, Edward Chih-You, Identification and Characterization of a gene that is differentially expressed during Late B Lymphocyte Development., September, 1991 (Box 3)
  - Timmins, William Nathaniel, Studies on the Stability of the Clinical Eog.., June, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Velculescu, Victor E., Identification of an Endosome Retention Signal in the 300 kD Mannose-6-Phosphate Receptor.., May 28, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Wong, Carolyn, An Enhancer Trap Screen in search of Downstream Targets of the Homeotic-selector Gene Sex Combs Reduced.., June 1992 (Box 3)
  - Wu, Sean Ming-Yuan, Neutromuscular Adaption to Changes in Body Orientation with Respect to Gravity During One-legged Cycling.., May 1992 (Box 3)
- Theses, Accession ARCH-1993-062
  - Agersborg, Sally S., Antigen Presentation by Resting B Cells May Induce T Cell Tolerance to a Determinant of Sperm Whale Myoglobin., June, 1993 (Box 1)
  - Aghi, Manish, The Role of the Integrin d4B7 in Lymphocyte Retention in the Sleen., June, 1993 (Box 1)
  - Alpern, Eytan, Steel Factor Influences the Distribution, Cycle Status, and Stem Cell Acitivity of Murine Hematopietic Stem Cells in vivo., May, 1993 (Box 1)
  - Baron, Miriam, Characterization of Ligands Recognized by vdT Cell Receptors., June 1993 (Box 1)
  - Bell, Russell, Determining the Changes in Biodivesity of Forbs and Soil Fauna Due to Selective Timber Harvesting in the Santa Cruz Redwood Forest., June, 1993 (Box 1)
  - Briscoe, Adriana Darielle Mejia, Populational, structural and regulatory properties of EST-D in colias butterflies., May 1993 (Box 1)
  - Chang, David J., Role of Major Histocompatibility Complex in the Immunological Response to Schistosomiasis: Morphological Characterization of Granuloma Formation and Cytokine Profiles of Infected Mince.., June 1993 (Box 1)
  - Chen, Henry Albert, In vivo evidence that Benzodiazepine receptor heterogeneity, rather than partial agonism at a single receptor, is responsible for the selective behavioral action of these Benzodiazepine receptor ligands.., June 1993 (Box 1)
  - Chiang, Scott Kevin, Linkage Mapping of Transposable Markers in the pRmeSU47a Megaplasmid of Rhizobium meliloti.., June 1993 (Box 1)
  - Conn, Erika Vienna, Mitochondrial DNA Sequencing as a Method for the Determination of Relative Time Since Evolutionary Divergence of Two Butterfly Species: Phoebis agarithe and Phoebis sennae.., June 1993 (Box 1)
  - Dalal, Malika Pankaj, Characterization of the ATP-induced Chloride Pathway in HT29 Cells.., March 1993 (Box 1)
  - Danial, Nika Nelly, Differential Repair of Cyclobutane Pyrimidine Dimers in Wild Type and tranlocated Alleles of the c-myc Oncogene in Burkitt Lymphoma ST486 Cells.., June 1993 (Box 1)
  - Fuchs, Julie Robin, Circadian Rhythms in Somatostatin Levels in the Suprachiasmatic Nuclei of the Hypothalamus.., March 1993 (Box 1)
  - Gelber, Shari E., CZE Analysis of Spatial Storage and Release of Neuropeptides from the Bag Cells of Aplysia californica.., September 1992 (Box 1)
  - Gensch, erin M., Characterization of a Trk A Splice Variant., June 1992 (Box 1)
  - Gupta, Neelima, Ultrasound Does Not Enhance Doxo-Rubicin Cytotoxicity in 3T3 Multi-Drug Resistant Cells.., June 1993 (Box 1)
  - Gym, Aimee, Xeroderma Pigmentosum Group E Binding Factor?: Which Chemical Adducts Does It recognize?., June 1993 (Box 1)
  - Han, Jay J., Antisense RNA Approach to reducing the Levels of Synaptotagmin, N-synaptobrevin, and Rab3 in Drosophilia melanogaster.., May 1993 (Box 1)
  - Harper, Kimberly, The Relationship of MDR P-Glycoprotein and the Swelling-Activated Chloride Channel.., March 1993 (Box 1)
  - Hobday, Alistair, Body-size Variation Exhibited by an Intertidal Limpet: Influence of Wave Exposure, Tidal Height, and Migratory Behavior.., June 1993 (Box 2)
  - Hoh, Brian L., Examination of Viral Factors for the Transactivation of the 2.7-Kilobase RNA Promoter of Human Cytomegalovirus.., May 1993 (Box 2)
  - Itakura, Haruka, Detection and Analysis of Radiation Induced DNA-damage by a Polymerase Chain Reaction Approach in Human Cells.., June 1993 (Box 2)
  - Iyengar, Vijay K., The Guanine-Nucleotide-Binding-Protein Repertoire of B.Lymphocytes: a Novel G-protein found associated with the B cell receptor complex.., June 1993 (Box 2)
  - Jackman, Robin M., Development of an in-vitro Recombination Assay to Characterize the Minimal Recombination Site in Phage21.., December 1992 (Box 2)
  - Kang, Lana, Adipogenic Conversion and Spontaneous Foci Formation of Agouti-Expressing Fibroblast Cells: In Vitro assays for Function of the Agouti Gene Product.., June 1993 (Box 2)
  - Karpati, Ronit Lilian, Use of 2-Deoxyglucose Double Pulse in Determining the Role of Neurons and Glia in the Suprachiasmatic Nuclei Pacemaker Activity.., June 1993 (Box 2)
  - Kim, Dewey T., The Effect of T Cell Affinity on T Cell Activation.., June 3, 1993 (Box 2)
  - Kim, Joanne Jung-Yun, Foraging Demand effects on Social Behavior and Pituitary-Adrenal Activity in Juvenile Squirrel Monkeys.., June 1993 (Box 2)
  - Kim, Louis Y., Apoptosis: Evaluating the Response of Human B and T Cancer Cell Lines to Aphidicolin.., June 1993 (Box 2)
  - Kodali, Susheel, Al Adenosine Receptor Stimulation increases EEG Delat power in the Rat.., June 1993 (Box 2)
  - Laane, Christina J., Effects of Fasting on Low Density Lipoprotein Receptors in Adipose and Hepatic Tissues of Rats.., June 1993 (Box 2)
  - Lam, Naomi K., A Mechanism of Metal Carcinogenesis: The Region Most Conserved Among alpha-like DNA Polymerases is Involved in Metal-Induced DNA Synthetic Infidelity.., June 1993 (Box 2)
  - Lee, Cadir Batista, Purification of Hepatocyte Growth Factor and Characterization of its Interaction with E-Amino Caproic Acid., May 27, 1993 (Box 2)
  - Lee, Grace Ann, Identification of the Bacterial Attachment Site of Phage 21., June, 1993 (Box 2)
  - Lentine, Krista, The Coupling of Transcription and Replication in Caulobacter crescentus., June, 1993 (Box 2)
  - Li, Michelle L., Racemization of Aspartate Residues in GFPA, MBP, and PLP Isolated from Alzheimer's Disease and Multiple Sclerosis Brains., June, 1993 (Box 2)
  - Lim, Jonathan, In Vitro Studies of Hox-Bl (Hox 2.9) in Human Embryonic Kidney-293 Cells Provide Evidence for Positive Autogenous Regulation., May, 1993 (Box 2)
  - Lim, Lee Paul, Attempt at Assaying In Vivo Repair of a Plasmid Damaged In Vitro., June, 1993 (Box 2)
  - Lin, Hubert S., Vasoactive Intestinal Peptide Release from Cultures Cells of the Rat Suprachiasmatic Nucleus., June, 1993 (Box 2)
  - Lin, Michelle, DNA Repair Effciency Between 3' and 5' Regions of the DHFR Gene in UV-Irradiated Human Cells as Indicator of Transcriptional Activity., June 3, 1993 (Box 2)
  - Lizaso, Knef Villena, Identification of I-Ag7-binding Peptides Derived from Carboxypeptidase H, an Autoantigen in Insulin-Dependent Diabetes Mellitus., June, 1993 (Box 2)
  - Meneshian, Avedis, Design of a Computerized Monitoring System for Use in Further Development of the Thermal Balance Model of Colias Butterflies: Preliminary Analysis of the "Reflectance Basking Hypothesis"., June, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Mikulec, Anthony, An In Vitro Whole Mount Corneal Preparation to Examine the Effects of EGF, Subsatnce P, and CGRP on Corneal Epithelial Wound Healing., March, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Mukherjee, Siddhartha, A Screen for Target Sequences of Yeast Endogenous Transcriptional Activators.., June 4, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Nelson, Dvora, The Negative Feedback System of the Hypothalamic-Pituitary-Adrenal Axis in the Developing Rat.., June 1993 (Box 3)
  - Oei, Tommy, Comparison of the Effects of Propranolol on the mating Behavior in Three Strains of Male Rats: SHR, WKY, and Long-Evans.., June 1993 (Box 3)
  - Patil, Chiristopher Kashinath, Nucleotide excision repair in the early embryo: Development of an experimental system in Lytechinus pictus.., June 1993 (Box 3)
  - Pickart, Michael Cahill, Changes in the Vasculature's Response to ANP and CNP Following Injury.., June 1993 (Box 3)
  - Rodrguez, Lizel, In vitro Pharmacological Characterization of Fentanyl Opioid Analogs.., June 1993 (Box 3)
  - Sangha, Simren, The Generation of Neurons and Astrocytes from a Common Precursor Cell in the Rat Cortex.., June 1993 (Box 3)
  - Sauer, Frederic G., MHC Class II Non-coding Regions: A comparison of the Mouse A-alpha and E-alpha Genes.., June 1993 (Box 3)
  - Schindler, Joshua, Identification of Novel Substrates for the Hepatocyte Growth Factor Receptor.., June 1993 (Box 3)
  - Shu, Huidy, Localization of the Cystic Fibrosis Transmembrane Conductance Regulator in the Human Liver.., June 2, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Siao, Pauline, Localization of CFTR in Transfected 3T3 Cells with Polyclonal Antibodies., June, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Sison, Aimee Lee V., A Gene Influencing Midgut Development in Drosophila melanogaster.., June, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Sohn, Susan H., The Role of Lck Kinase in T-Cell Signal Transduction.., June, 1993 (Box 4)
  - Stoffel, John, The use of High Pressure liquid Chromatography for Identifying the Biliberdin IX Isomer(s) Produced by Higher Plant Heme Oxygenase., June, 1993 (Box 4)
  - Suen, Jeffrey, Structural and functional comparisons of the Drosophila cirilis and Drosophila menlanogaster oskar gene.., June, 1993 (Box 4)
  - Sukumvanich, Paniti, Sequencing and Analysis of PKC-0, a Novel Member of the PRotein Kinase-C Famil mainly expressed in T-Cells among the Hematopoietic Cells.., June, 1993 (Box 4)
  - Sullivan, Daniel P., Directions of Migration in the Developing Visual Cortex.., June, 1993 (Box 4)
  - Tsai, Larry Wilse, Testosterone Induces a Fast Increase in Muscle Cell Metabolism.., June 2, 1993 (Box 4)
  - White, Rebekah, Heterologous Regulation of Steroid Hormone Receptor Abundance May Be a Mechanism for Modulating Target Cell Responsiveness.., June 1993 (Box 4)
  - Wong, Clifford, The Production of Hydroxyl Radicals Induced by Glutamate Receptor Activation in Culture.., March 1993 (Box 4)
  - Yeh, Michael W., Glucocoricoids Exacerbate Kainate-Induced Spectrin Proteolysis in a Dose-Dependent Manner.., May 1993 (Box 4)
  - Yeh, S,Eileen, Effects of Methabolic Inhibitation in the Suprachiasmatic Nuclei and Anterior Hypothalamus.., June 1993 (Box 4)
  - Yilmaz, Lal P., Induction of Apoptosis Through Continuous Short-term Exposure to Colcemid in Human Cancer Cell Lines CEM, Tera-2, and HeLa S3.., June 1993 (Box 4)
  - Yoo, Charles, Analysis of Cloned cDNA Fragments in the 3' Region of Slow Myosin 3.., June 1993 (Box 4)
  - Young, Kimberly Allison, Gene Expression in Rat Brain During Sleep Deprivation.., March 1993 (Box 4)
  - Yung, Jeffrey Chan, Cytokine Regulation in the CD 4+ Cells of Allergic and Non-allergic Individuals.., June 1, 1993 (Box 4)
- Theses, Accession ARCH-1994-082